

CONTACT



+49 174 735 0439



michaelmarsh993@gmail.com



Hamburg, DE



michaelmarsh.github.io

SKILLS

MS Word, MS Excel

Dart, Python, JavaScript

Flutter, Firebase, MatLab

....

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

GERMAN

SPANISH

.

HOBBIES







Michael Marsh

Goal-oriented research and development professional with five years of experience in fast-paced environments. Key strengths include data research, user experience programming, scientific writing, project management, and organizational skills. Seeking to use my expertise in a growing business. Ready to help achieve company goals through team work and international cooperation.

EDUCATION

M.Sc. Biomechanics

2018-present

Ruhr University Bochum

B.Sc. Kinesiology

2012-2018

California State University, Long Beach

EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant

2018-2020

Ruhr University Bochum

Collect, Analyze, and Write Reports for Biomechanics Department

Personal Fitness Trainer

2016-2018

Equinox, Huntington Beach, CA

Prescribe Exercise and Nutritional Plans for Clientele

Vitamin Department Manager

2014-2016

Sprouts Farmers Market, Huntington Beach, CA

Supervise, Maintain Stock, Oversee Scheduling for Department

Published Research

Triceps surae torque-length relationships relevant for walking activity levels with and without an ankle exoskeleton

Hessel, A. et al. 2019